(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord.
(Penny:)- We have to go.
- Not now, this poor man needs me.
(Sheldon:)You, hold on, I'll be right with you.
(Sheldon:)What computer do you have,
and please don't say a white one.
- Excuse me.
- Fill this out and have a seat.
(Howard:)We're throwing
my friend a surprise party...
(Howard:)...and I'm supposed to keep him out
for two hours.
(Nurse:)Uh-huh. Fill this out and have a seat.
The way I could get him
to leave was tell him I ate a peanut.
(Howard:)I'm allergic to peanuts.
(Nurse:)Well, in that case,
fill this out and have a seat.
(Howard:)All I need from you
is to give me a BAND-AID.
I can pretend I had epinephrine.
(Howard:)Tell my friend you need to keep me
under observation for an hour.
- Is that all you need?
- Yes.
(Nurse:)Get out of my ER.
- No, you don't understand.
- I understand.
(Nurse:)But unfortunately, this hospital
is not equipped to treat stupid.
(Howard:)Okay, I get it.
I know how the world works.
(Howard:)How about if I were to introduce you
to the man who freed your people?